[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The tail assembly of 747 stands the height of a building of approximately how many stories?", "correct_answer": "approx. 6 stories", "incorrect_answers": ["approx. 8 stories", "approx. 4 stories", "approx. 2 stories"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Johnny Crawford was born in Las Vegas, Nevada.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The item that  the villain sent M in the film The Man With The Golden Gun was made where?", "correct_answer": "Macau", "incorrect_answers": ["Jakarta", "Rangoon", "Kuala Lumpur"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Chinese mythology, what shape do fox spirits known as huli jing take in the real world?", "correct_answer": "Women", "incorrect_answers": ["Cats", "Children", "Bushes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What flower remedy would be most beneficial to a stand-offish horse that gets irritated quickly and has a hard time accepting change?", "correct_answer": "Beech", "incorrect_answers": ["Birch", "Cerery", "Cerato"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Brandy Separators are made with this coffee-flavored liqueur.", "correct_answer": "Kahlua", "incorrect_answers": ["Creme de Cacao", "Baileys", "Frangelico"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which term is defined as fear of crowds, public places or open areas?", "correct_answer": "Agoraphobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Aviophobia", "None of these", "Claustrophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In May 2008, this painter set a new world record for sale value of a painting by a living artist when Benefits Supervisor Sleeping was sold for $33.6 million. What is his/her name?", "correct_answer": "Lucian Freud", "incorrect_answers": ["Simon Francis", "Clinton Ford", "Brian Froud"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of wood did Noah build the ark out of?", "correct_answer": "Gopher", "incorrect_answers": ["Oak", "Ash", "Cedar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of meal is the traditional Japanese dish called Zoni?", "correct_answer": "Soup", "incorrect_answers": ["Dessert", "Fried fish", "Sushi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which breed group does the Chinese Crested dog belong to?", "correct_answer": "Toy", "incorrect_answers": ["Sporting", "Hound", "Non-Sprint"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these Disney characters go together?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Mickey and Minnie", "Cinderella and Charming", "Lady and Tramp"]}]